当你仍然单身
when you're single,
但你的朋友们却陆续结婚时
and your friends start to get married,
每一个婚礼邀请都是一次自我挑战
every wedding invitation presents a strange\nmoment of self-evaluation:
"您将带嘉宾出席
"Will you be bringing a guest,
还是独自出席?"
or will you be attending alone?"
真正问的是
What it's really asking is,
"3个月内去找个
"where do you see yourself in three months
坐在旁边的女朋友
Sitting next to your girlfriend,
还是去追伴娘?"
or hitting on a bridesmaid?"
我向来都是选择带嘉宾
I always checked that I was bringing a guest.
我是个乐观主义者
I was an optimist.
两个月26天后
two months and 26 days later.
我该带谁去这婚礼呢?
Who the hell am I gonna bring to this wedding?
Ted, 你忘了我教你的吗?
Ted,have you ignored all my teachings?
大部分是
For the most part,yeah.
不, 你不能带伴去婚礼
No,you don't bring a date to a wedding.
这就象拖着只鹿的尸体去打猎
That's like bringing a deer carcass on a hunting trip.
噢 Ted 噢 Ted
oh,Ted. oh,Ted.
别 别带伴
No,no date.
鹿尸? 真的吗?
Deer carcass? Really?
你在暗示你要带去吗?
That's the metaphor you're going with here?
Ted, 这只是个比喻
Ted,it's a simile.
已经太晚了
it's too late now.
如果我不带个伴
If I don't bring a date,
一份200块的鸡肉或鲑肉就没人吃了
a $200 piece of chicken/salmon\nwill go uneaten.
我得带个人去, 但带谁呢?
I got to bring someone,but who?
当然, 我知道我想带谁去
Of course,I knew who I wanted to bring.
Robin\nRobin
不用想也知道的答案
the big unanswered question in my life.
问题是
Problem was,
她在和那个叫Derek的有钱家伙约会
she was dating this really rich guy named Derek.
Derek.\nDerek.
嗯, 我和Derek刚分手了
Well,Derek and I just broke up.
噢, 太糟糕了!
no,that's terrible!
你还好吧?
are you okay?
你要喝点酒或者什么吗?
do you need a drink or something?
我们不怎么合拍
we never really clicked.
但我还是满难过的
I felt bad,though.
他非常沮丧
He was pretty bummed.
别责怪自己
don't beat yourself up.
他会好起来的
He'll be fine.
我说, 那家伙, 是个亿万富翁
I mean,the guy's,like,a billionaire.
他可以把他的白金卡放到钓线上
He can put his platinum card\non a fishing line
钓10条比你性感的美女
and reel in ten chicks hotter than you.
谢谢 我感觉好多了
Thanks. I feel a lot better.
我想我要去喝点酒了
I think I'll get that drink now.
好了, 伙计们, 我有话要说
Okay,guys,I got to say something.
我觉得我对Robin的感觉又回来了
I think my feelings for Robin\nmay be resurfacing.
拜托 难道你还想死灰复燃
please,they were buried in a shallow grave.
别又来
Not again.
拜托
Come on.
伙计?
Dude?
我们都知道电影的结果会怎样
We all know how this movie ends.
Ted坠入爱河
Ted falls in love,
Ted在萌芽期就被打击，然后就是滚动演员表
love kicks Ted in the sprouts,roll credits.
不对, 你们看看这些画面就知道了
No,you guys just have to look\nat the whole picture.
场景: Robin对我一见钟情
fact:Robin was into me when we first met.
场景: 尽管她不想交男朋友
fact:Even though she didn't want\na relationship,
我们还是在屋顶来了个热吻
we had an amazing kiss on the roof.
场景: 新年夜
fact:On New Year's Eve,
我们又接吻了
we kissed again.
场景: 我需要一个伴陪我去这个婚礼
fact:I need a date to this wedding.
祝我好运吧
Wish me luck.
我不明白的是为什么Claudia要嫁给Stuart?
What I don't get is why is Claudia\nmarrying Stuart?
她比他漂亮多了
She's way hotter than him.
多多少?
How way?
多多了
Way way.
但这个婚礼还是让人那么向往
This wedding does sound pretty amazing,though.
高级酒店舞厅
Fancy hotel ballroom,
每个人都盛装打扮...
everybody all dressed up...
来吧
here we go.
什么?
What?
我们找不到满意的婚礼举行地
We can't get anywhere with our wedding plans
因为我想找有趣的的地方\n而Marshall喜欢土气
because I want it to be fun and Marshall\nwants it to be lame.
好吧, 这说法真公平
Okay,that's a pretty fair assessment\nof our two arguments.
我也觉得
I thought so.
知道吗?
You know what?
抱歉 如果我不想赤脚在
Excuse me, if I don't want to get\nmarried barefoot
在车都开不进去的河边森林结婚
in the woods next to lake no-one's-\ngoing- to-drive-that-far.
是的
Yes.
我想要在舞厅
I want a ballroom,
想要支乐队, 还想要有鞋穿
and I want a band,and I want shoes.
我一直梦想着这天自从我还是个...
I've been dreaming about this day\nsince I was,like...
小女孩?
a little girl?
厉害!
what up!
好吧 我只是想说这也是我的婚礼
Okay.I'm just saying that it's\nmy wedding,too,
我得发表点意见
and I should have a say in it.
对啊, 但我才是新娘, 所以我说的算
Yes,but I'm the bride,so I win.
我认为婚姻是两个平等的伴侣一起共渡余生
I thought marriage was about two\nequal partners sharing a life together.
对啊, 但我才是新娘, 所以我说的算
Right,but I'm the bride,so I win.
我说, 真的是Claudia和Stuart?
I mean,seriously,Claudia and Stuart?
我是说, 我也交往过
I mean,I've hooked up with the odd lass
低于我魅力等级的女工
who was beneath my level of attractiveness,
但, 我当时喝醉了
but,you know,I was drunk.
没道理Claudia醉酒了3年吧
There's no way Claudia has been drunk\nfor three years.
你知道, 我一直认为忘记失恋痛苦
You know,I've always found that the best way
的最好方法是去
to get over a failed relationship is
庆祝他人的美满生活
to celebrate someone else's successful one.
有道理
it makes sense.
那么, 你也这样想
So,with that in mind,
我们的朋友Claudia和Stuart周六举行个挺正式的婚礼
our friends Claudia and Stuart are having\nthis crazy black-tie wedding on Saturday.
你想当我的嘉宾吗?
You want to be my plus one?
"嘉宾" 你说的真浪漫
"plus one." You make it sound so romantic.
好了
Fine.
那你愿意当我的伴吗?
You want to be my date?
你的伴?
Your date?
我很乐意
I'd love to.
这个婚礼到底多隆重?
How fancy are we talking about here?
你可能要带上你最好的行头
you're going to want to\nbring your "A" game.
噢 我会的
Oh,I'll bring it.
我会穿得很抢眼
I'll bring it so hard,
让新娘看起来象个白色袋子装起来的螃蟹
the bride's going to look like a big white bag of crap.
Lily?\nLily?
我需要件礼服
I need a dress.
你要去吗?
you're going?
太棒了!
That's awesome!
我的天
my god
四天内找到礼服?
four days to find a dress?
我知道, 这会让人想自杀
I know,it's a suicide mission.
如果我们现在就开始...
if we leave now...
我们还有机会胜利
we can still have a fighting chance.
来吧!
Let's do it!
拜, 宝贝
Bye,babe.
你们看她多有激情?
Did you see how fired up she was?
我不知道, 已经有点什么了
I don't know,there's something there.
等到周六
And,come Saturday,
来点音乐, 舞蹈,几杯香槟...
a little music,a little dancing, a lot of champagne...
谁知道会怎样?
who knows?
Ted, 你得再去认识个绅士了
Ted,you're going to have to find another gender for yourself,
因为我要废了你的"兄弟"会员卡
cause I'm revoking your "dude"\nmembership.
耶, 昨天你修甲修的怎么样?
Yeah,how was that manicure yesterday?
不错, 谢谢
Invigorating,thanks.
好吧, 我不会在他们面前说这些
Okay,I wasn't going to say it in front of the guys,
但我那时候真的认为事情会发展的很顺利
but back then I really thought that's how it worked.
和你喜欢的女孩在浪漫的地方...
You put yourself and a girl you like\nin some romantic setting...
...灯光闪烁...
...the stars line up...
可惜眨眼就没
and shazam.
我知道现实从来不会这么简单达成
I know now that life is never that\nsimple.
嘿, Claudia!
Hey,Claudia!
对, 我要塔希提香草!
yes,I want tahitian vanilla!
你写错了吗?
You wrote it down wrong?
不对, 不对, 听我说
No,no,no,no,listen to me
如果我发现婚礼上蛋糕不是塔希提香草味的
if I go to my wedding and the cake is not tahitian vanilla,
我会去你那把店给拆了!
I will come down there and\nburn your little shop to the ground!
你想试下我是不是开玩笑吗?
Do you want to find out if I'm kidding?
再见
good-bye.
怎么样了?
How's it going?
我的婚礼就在两天后了
My wedding is in two days,
就这样
that's how it's going.
别担心, 会很棒的
don't worry,it's going to be great.
我很期待
I'm so excited.
你当然会
you should be
大把的单身女孩
lots of single girls.
我会...
I'm...
带个伴去
bringing a date,
所以那些与我无关了
so I'll be off the market.
什么?
What?
我要带着伴去
I'm bringing a date.
你不会带
You're not bringing a date.
不, 我会
yes,I am.
不, 你不会
no,you're not.
我填了"带嘉宾"
I checked "plus one."
没, 你没有
No,you didn't.
Claudia, 我很确定我有填...
Claudia,I'm pretty sure I checked...
Ted, 你没有填 "带嘉宾"!
Ted,you did not check "plus one"!
你不能带着伴来我婚礼!
You are not bringing a date to my wedding!
我已经邀请人了
But I already invited someone.
你不会带嘉宾来, Ted!
you are not bringing a guest,Ted!
嘉宾名单几个月前就确定了
The guest list has been closed for months
几个月!
months!
但我有填 "带嘉宾"!
But I checked "plus one"!
我一直都是填"带嘉宾"!
I always check "plus one"!
你绝对没有填\n"带嘉宾"!
You absolutely did not check\n"plus one"!
如果你填的是"带嘉宾"
If you had checked "plus one,"
我会致电给你索要嘉宾姓名
I would have called you to get\nthe name of your guest,
以便座位上放置名牌
so I could have the place cards\nprind up.
我有找你要你的嘉宾姓名吗?
Did I call you to get the name\nof your guest?
有印着她名字的名牌吗?
Is there a place card with her\nname printed on it?
她不需要名牌
She doesn't need a place card.
她知道自己叫什么
She knows her name.
那她吃什么?!
What's she eating?!
你定了鸡肉
You ordered the chicken.
她有什么?
What did she order?
你知道你的故事有多少漏洞吗?
Do you see how your story is\nfull of holes?
拜托, Claudia, 我们回到正事吧
Come on,Claudia,we go way back.
就没有一个多出来的位置吗?
Isn't there room for just one\nmore person?
别逼我出手, Ted
Don't make me hurt you,Ted.
我不敢相信!
I don't believ this!
Claudia疯了!
Claudia's crazy!
但, 公平来说
But,to be fair,
她也很性感\n我明明填了"带嘉宾"
she's also hot \nI totally checked "plus one."
我确定
I'm sure I did.
是啊\n我有填!
right.\nI did!
耶，我不觉得你有
Yeah,I don't think you did.
知道为什么吗?
You know why?
因为你内心深处
Because deep down,
不想带着嘉宾参加婚礼
you didn't want to show up at\nthis thing with a date.
你说了那么多关于准备好交女朋友的谎话
See,for all your big talk about being ready for a relationship,
归根结底你还是单身
deep down,you're single.
这是你的"默认设置"
It's your "default setting".
Ted, 你知道你脑袋深处?
Ted,you know what's in the back of your brain?
噢天, "小Barney"演说又来了
great,here comes the little Barney speech.
秘密的
Behind a curtain,
有一小处地方偷偷控制着你的行动?
in a dark little room secretly controlling your every move?
小Barney...
A Little Barney...
小Barney
a little Barney.
知道他说什么吗?
And you know what he said?
"Ted... "\n"Ted... "
"你不会带着伴参加这个婚礼"
you will bring no dates to this wedding.
"你... "
"You... "
"你将和正常大小的Barney一起泡醉酒的伴娘"
will hit on drunk bridesmaids with actual-size Barney."
别说了
Please stop.
我要去给Claudia打电话
I got to call Claudia.
- 如果我对她解释...\n- Ted, 别!
-If I just explain to her...\n-Ted,no!
算了吧
Let it go.
她要结婚了
She's about to get married,
有够多的事情得操心了
she's got enough to worry about.
那我该怎么办?
Then what am I going to do?
你能做的只有
The only thing you can do
告诉Robin她不能去了
tell Robin she can't come.
等一下!
Just a second!
- 听着...\n- 等等, 两件事
- Listen...\n- wait,two things.
首先...
First of all...
我整个下午都在为你"打基础"
I have been laying groundwork all afternoon.
非常微妙地, 沉着地不催, 也不明显暗示
Totally subtle,totally cool,not pushing,not even nudging,
都是为了今天的主题,"Ted最棒"
just: The theme of today is,"Ted rocks."
她正慢慢中我的计
And she's picking up what I'm laying down.
- Lily,现在有问题是... !\n- 等等, 别
- Lily,there's a problem... !\n- Wait,no.
第二件事: 礼服
Thing number two: The dress.
我们找到了礼服
We got a dress.
去吧
Go.
这样行了吧, 还是...
Did I bring it,or...
这样行了吧?
did I bring it?
我确实穿了最好的行头
I think I brought it.
就是为了这个
That's what I was going for.
我太期待明天了
I'm so excited about tomorrow.
明天我们会很开心
We're going to have so much fun.
关于这个...
about that...
我五点来接你
I'll pick you up at 5:00.
嗯? 礼服怎么样?
so? The dress?
我不能带嘉宾去婚礼
I don't have a plus one for the wedding.
什么?
What?
我碰见Claudia
I ran into Claudia,
她告诉我我没有在回复卡上填"带嘉宾"
and she told me I didn't check\n"plus one" on the reply card.
为什么你没填 "带..."?
Why didn't you check "plus..."?
我有填 "带嘉宾"
I did check "plus one."
Robin这么期待
But Robin is so excited.
我知道
I know.
还有礼服!
And the dress!
我知道
I know.
好吧, 好吧
okay,okay.
我们把她偷偷弄进去
we'll sneak her in.
我们不能把她偷偷弄进去
We can't sneak her in,
我们又不是忍者
we're not ninjas.
真希望我们是忍者
I wish we were ninjas.
我知道
I know.
你可以去问下Stuart
You could always ask Stuart.
可以这样吗?
Can I do that?
当然
sure.
你们那么久的朋友了
You guys have been friends for a long time.
而且那婚礼他占4成
And it's 40% his wedding,too.
我不知道...
I don't know...
这可不太好谈
it's going to be a tough sell.
伙计, 没问题
Dude,no problem whatsoever.
真的吗?
Really?
当然, 越多越好
Sure,the more,the merrier.
谢谢你这样通融
thanks for being so cool about this,
因为Claudia说...
cause you know,Claudia said...
今天早晨演练时
This morning at the rehearsal,
Claudia骂我们7岁的花童是婊子
Claudia called our seven-year-old\nflower girl a whore.
所以, 别生气
So,don't take it personally,
她只是压力太大了
she's just a little stressed.
她一般不是这样的
she's not usually like that.
是啊
No.
谢谢, Stu!
thanks,Stu!
婚礼会很棒的
It's going to be a great wedding.
亲爱的, 这杂志上说越来越多的夫妻
Honey,this magazine says more and more couples are opting
选择在树林里举行非传统的婚礼
to have non-traditional weddings out in the woods.
如果杂志都这样说了
if a magazine says so,
我们应该在树林里结婚
we should go get married in the woods,
就象松鼠一样
like a couple of squirrels.
松鼠才不会结婚, Marshall
Squirrels don't get married,Marshall.
好象你就知道似的
Like you could possibly know that.
我做到了
I did it.
I did it
我要带她去婚礼
I'm taking her to the wedding.
很好!
Nice!
什么? 怎么带?
What? How?
我找Stuart了
I talked to Stuart.
你找新郎下手
you went around the bride.
"噢, 这些黄蜂窝似乎无害
"Oh,this hornets' nest looks harmless.
也许我可以用木棍去捅捅"
Maybe I'll poke it with a stick."
"噢, 看, 有小妖精
"Oh,look,some gremlins.
我们午夜后来喂他们!"
Let me go feed them after midnight!"
你知道这些吗?
Did you know about this?
那可能是我的主意
It may have been my idea.
什么?
what?
Stuart就不能作主吗?
Stuart doesn't get a say?
所以你同意了
So you admit it
新郎有同等的权利
the groom should have an equal say.
当然, 在一些蠢事上, 象邀请谁
sure,on the stupid stuff,like who comes.
所以我随便邀请谁都行吗?
So I can invite whoever I want?
当然, 树林里空间很大
Sure,there's plenty of room in the woods.
是Claudia
it's Claudia.
来了
So it begins.
拜托, 不会那么糟的
Come on,it can't be that bad.
来, Lily, 你来听
here,Lily,you answer it.
什么? 为什么?
What? Why?
因为这都是你的主意
Because this whole thing was your idea.
而且...我很怕Claudia
And... Claudia scares me.
但... 你才是...
But... but you're the...
但我只是想...
but I just want...
Ted的电话
Ted's phone.
嗨 Claudia
Hi Claudia.
什么?
What?
我不在场
Now I wasn't there,
但从我听到的判断
but from what I heard,
事情是这样的...
it went something like this...
还有, 亲爱的
by the way,honey,
Ted来过我告诉他可以带着伴来婚礼
Ted stopped by and I told him he could bring his date to the wedding.
你说什么?
You what?
...老是在背后拖我后腿...
...always undermining me at every turn...
...试着变通一下
...try to show a little flexibility,
但你没有!
but no!
全是考虑你!
It's all about you!
...还有你妈...
...and your mother...
你知道吗?
you know what?
婚礼取消!
The wedding's off!
他们分手了
they broke up!
不是我的错, 是不?
It's not because of me,is it?
我爸已经为这婚礼花了很多钱了!
And my dad already paid for this huge wedding!
他会杀了我的!
he's going to kill me!
然后他会去杀了Ted!
And then he's gonna kill Ted!
我也会去杀了Ted
Then I'm gonna kill Ted.
是Robin
it's Robin.
接!
Answer it!
Lily的电话
Lily's phone.
Ted, Lily呢?
Ted,where's Lily?
我要告诉她我买的很棒的鞋
I need to tell her about these awesome shoes I just bought.
Lily现在很忙
Lily's busy.
好吧, 我只想说鞋很漂亮,Ted会喜欢它们的
okay,I just wanted to say they're\ngorgeous d Ted's going to love them.
很好
That's great,
我会让Lily转告我
I'll tell Lily to tell me.
听着, 我很想继续聊
listen,I really want to keep talking,
但现在时机不对
but now's not a good time,
还有我很期待明天好了, 拜
so I'm really excited about tomorrow,okay,bye.
好, 拜
Okay,bye.
糟糕, 她买了双很贵的鞋
Crap,she bought some expensive shoes.
她真的很期待这个
She's really looking forward to this.
你认为她喜欢我吗?
Do you think she's into me?
Ted, 注意!
Ted,focus!
好, 好了, 甜心, 冷静
Okay,okay,sweetie,just calm down.
你想去什么地方谈谈吗?
Do you want to go somewhere and talk?
我想去找个地方喝酒!
I want to go somewhere and drink!
好, Maclaren见
Okay,meet me at Maclaren's.
我去那找你
I'll see you there.
我感觉很糟糕
I feel terrible.
晚点再难过
feel terrible later.
现在, 我们要先让他们复合
Right now,we gotta fix this.
Lily, 你去酒吧安慰Claudia
Lily,you go down to the bar\nand comfort Claudia.
我和Ted去找Stuart谈谈
Ted and I will go and try\nto talk some sense into Stuart.
好
Right.
告诉Claudia我很抱歉
tell Claudia I'm sorry.
她有怪我吗?
Did she seem pissed at me?
她说如果明天不举行婚礼
She said if there's no wedding tomorrow,
你就欠她爸40万
you owe her father $400,000.
看看怎样才能让这两个小疯子和好?
What say we get these crazy kids\nback together?
嗨 悲伤的眼神
Hi,sad eyes.
为什么这么失落?
What's got you down?
我和Stuart刚分手了
Stuart and I just broke up.
噢天, 我很抱歉
Oh god,I'm so sorry.
这太, 这...
That's just,that's...
两杯草莓伏特加, 谢谢
two vodka cranberries,please.
你没忘记我是喝草莓伏特加
You remembered I drink vodka cranberries.
没忘记?
Remember?
是你啊, 我怎么能忘?
When it comes to you,how can I forget?
她们都喝草莓伏特加
They all drink vodka cranberries.
那么...
So...
还有什么需要的吗...
is there anything else you need...
甜心?
sweetie?
你有40万吗?
You got $400,000?
没有
No.
但我有双臂
But I do have a hug.
谢谢
Thank you.
Stuart, 我-我不知道说什么
Stuart,I-I don't know what to say.
如果是我导致这个...
If I caused this in any way...
Ted, 我所知道的
Ted,for all I know,
是你帮了我\n其他人都帮不了的大忙
you did me the biggest favor\nanyone's ever done me.
拜托, 伙计, 你不是那么想的
come on,man,you don't mean that.
不, 我是
No,I do
整个事情让我发现我想念单身生活
this whole thing has made me realize\nI miss being single.
我想念晚归
I miss staying out late,
和家里一团乱不去清理
and making messes and not cleaning them up.
我想念黄书
I miss owning porn.
伙计, 谁不会呢?
Dude,who doesn't?
还有, 我会遇见一些超级性感的模特\n我会想...
And you know,I'll see some\nsuper-hot model chick,and I'll think,
"为什么我和Claudia一起?
"why am I with Claudia?
我本来可以和她的"
I could be with her."
这太疯了!
That's just crazy!
我是说...
I mean...
你是最幸运...
you're the luckiest...
你和Claudia都是...
you and Claudia both...
重点是我想结婚
the point is I want to get married.
我想安定下来
I want to settle down,
但现在, 我不是我了
but right now,that's just not\nwho I am.
我不是一个懂承诺的人
I'm not a commitment guy;
我是个单身的人
I'm a single guy.
Stuart, 你不需要做任何人
Stuart,you don't have to be one\nor the other.
每个人都会有这种时候
Everybody feels this way sometimes.
一起生活并不简单
Relationships aren't easy;
需要很大努力
they're hard work.
这是关于包容
It's about compromise,
一起成长...等等Phil博士语录
growing together,all that Dr.Phil crap.
你怎么知道? 你都没结婚
How would you know?\nYou're not even married.
好吧, 问这家伙
Okay,ask this guy.
他和Lily在一起9年了
Nine years he's been with Lily.
他是准新郎 这家伙知道怎么处理
He's the pro,this guy knows relationships.
跟他说, Marshall
Tell him,Marshall.
Stuart, 别结婚
Stuart,don't get married.
- 伙计...\n- 什么?
- Dude...\n- what?
听着, 我很抱歉
Look,I'm sorry.
做夫妻很难
Being in a couple is hard.
承诺, 妥协, 都很难
And committing,making sacrifices,\nit's hard.
但如果是你的正确人选\n就会很容易
But if it's the right person,\nthen it's easy.
看着这女孩
Looking at that girl
知道她就是你一生至爱
and knowing she's all you really\nwant out of life,
这些事就顺理成章了
that should be the easiest thing\nin the world,
但如果不行
and if it's not like that,
那她就不是最合适的
then she's not the one.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你知道我没有40万, 是不?
You know I don't have $400,000,right?
也许我们结婚还太年轻了
Maybe we got together too young.
也许这就是问题所在
Maybe that's what the problem was.
我是说, 我28岁
I mean,I'm 28 years old,
只和一个男人在一起过
and I've really only ever been\nwith one man.
这太
that's just,
这...
that's...
再来两杯草莓伏特加, 谢谢!
two more vodka cranberries,please!
Claudia...\nClaudia...
会好起来的
it's all gonna be okay.
谢谢你听我说, Barney
thanks for listening,Barney.
对我来说很有帮助
it really means a lot to me.
我们象这样相遇...
Isn't it weird that we should...
会不会很怪?
run into each other like this?
两颗心
Two souls,
两个有同等级魅力的人
of equal levels of attractiveness,
就像磁铁一样互相吸引
both fitting together like two\npieces of a very attractive puzzle.
去死, 别想!
hell,no!
Claudia明天就要结婚了
Claudia is getting married tomorrow,
帮帮我
and so help me god,
如果被我抓到你和她呼吸同样的空气
if I catch you even so much as\nbreathing the same air as her,
我都会抓住你当睾丸用的"花生仁"
I will take those peanuts you're\ntrying to pass off as testicles,
我会使劲捏,让你痛得眼珠都突出来
and I will squeeze them so hard\nyour eyes pop out,
然后把它象葡萄一样喂给你!
and then I'll feed them to you\nlike grapes!
等等, 我的眼珠还是睾丸?
Wait,my eyes or my testicles?
一样一颗
One of each.
好吧! 好吧!
All right! All right!
Claudia?\nClaudia?
Stuart\nStuart.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我也很抱歉
I'm so sorry,too.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你, 宝贝
I love you too,babe.
Marshall和Ted让我看清了
Marshall and Ted set me straight.
当Marshall说我不要结婚时
And when Marshall told me not to marry you,
让我明白我...
it made me realize I...
Marshall说什么?!
Marshall said what?!
事情比你想的复杂!
It's more complicated than that!
他让我明白我有多爱你
He made me realize how much I love you.
他们让我们俩复合
These guys got us back together.
好了, 我没事了, 我没事了
Okay,I'm cool,I'm cool.
那我带嘉宾的事什么时候讨论?
So where did we land on the whole\nplus one thing?
别, 别, 别, 别!
no,no,no,no!
又叫了3杯草莓伏特加才让Claudia静下来
It took three more vodka Cranberries\nto subdue Claudia,
但, 最后
but,eventually,
她和善的同意了我带Robin去
she graciously agreed to let me\nbring Robin.
还是让人"哇"
Still wow.
你也是
Wow yourself.
看看你准备的行头
Look who else brought it.
我本来不想穿这样的
I thought about leaving it at home,
但我不想到那儿后
but I figured I don't want to get there
发现我需要它再跑回去拿
and realize I need it and have to\ngo all the way back to get it.
所以, 我穿来了
So,,I brought it.
抱歉
sorry.
喂?
Hello?
我的天 今晚?
my god.Tonight?
你开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
他们想要我今晚去代播新闻
They want me to anchor the news tonight.
真的吗?
Really?
真的代播?
Like anchor anchor?
Sandy怎么了?
what happened to Sandy?
好 好 当然
Okay. Okay. Sure.
要什么时候...
What time do you need me to...
就现在?!
right now?!
去吧
Do it.
好的, 我需要5分钟换衣服, 然后
Okay,I need like five minutes to change,and,
我在出租车上打给你...
I'll call you from the cab...
同意吧
so admit it.
这个在室内的婚礼同样精彩
This wedding is both indoors and amazing.
我会给你点虾肉糕
I'll give you the crab puffs.
那虾肉糕不错
The crab puffs are good.
那些虾肉糕让人难以置信
The crab puffs were incredible.
我们婚礼上也应该有
We should totally have them at our wedding.
当然...
Definitely...
嘿, 我们刚刚达成了某种共识
We just agreed on something.
我们开始谈论我们的婚礼了吗?
Did we just start planning our wedding?
我想是的
I think that we did.
我们也得那些棕色的酱汁
We totally have to get that brown dipping sauce.
我认为要红色那个,非常棒
I thought the red sauce was,like,awesome.
天, 你天生没有味蕾吗?
My god,were you born without taste buds?
什么?
what?
我爱你
I love you.
现在下一条新闻
coming up,
有蛇住在你们墙里面吗?
are there snakes living in your walls?
答案可能会吓到你...
The answer may surprise you...
休息后揭晓
after the break.
伙计, 你知道吗?
man,you know something?
Stuart是我的新英雄
Stuart's my new hero.
如果那家伙能娶一个可以打9分的
If that dude can bag a nine,
那我就可以找到16分的
I got to be able to bag,like,a 16.
16分是什么?
What's a 16?
那边两个8分的加起来
Those two eights right over there.
嗨 Ted
Hi Ted.
Claudia\nClaudia.
我们想和那位差点让我们分手的女士合影
We just wanted to get a picture with the\nwoman who almost ended our relationship.
她在哪?
where is she?
她没来
she couldn't make it.
有什么好笑的?
what's so funny?
去策划一个婚礼
plan a wedding.
你就知道了
You'll see.
看那边
Look at that.
应该那要才对
That's how it's supposed to be.
就那样
That right there.
容易, 简单
Easy,simple.
和Robin一起就不能那样
It's just not like that with Robin.
一点也不容易, 某种程度上来说
It's not easy,and on some level,
应该是很容易的
it has to just be easy.
说道容易...
Speaking of easy...
伴娘们, Ted
bridesmaids,Ted.
伴娘们
Bridesmaids.
顺便说下, 我差点忘了
By the way,I almost forgot.
我们找到这个
We found this.
我没有填 "带嘉宾"
I didn't check "plus one."
你是对的
You were right.
当然, 我是对的
Of course,I was right.
我单身
I'm single.
可能这就是我
Maybe that's just who I am.
你知道吗?
And you know what?
我喜欢单身
I like being single.
单身很好
Being single's the best.
想在外面待多晚都行
stay out as late as you want.
不用对谁交代
Answer to no one.
整个世界充满着无穷的可能性
The whole world full of endless possibilities.
永远不用去农贸市场
Never having to go to a farmer's market.
好了
Okay.
来点算术
doing some math here.
6号桌有3个伴娘
Table six has got three bridesmaids:
8分, 8分, 和一个7分
An eight,an eight,and a seven.
我很乐意给你一个8分的
I am willing to give you one of the eights,
让我降低到15分
lowering myself to a 15,
这表示你欠我...
which means you owe me...
这就是我们
so there we were,
两个单身的家伙
two single guys,
做着普通单身该做的事情
doing our usual single-guy thing.
因为某种原因
For whatever reason,
我让自己相信那晚是我的一个转折点
I had let myself believe that this night\nwould be a turning point,
今晚我的生活
that this was the night my life
我真正的生活
my real life
即将开始
would finally begin.
可笑的是...
The funny thing is...
我没完全错
I wasn't totally wrong.
因为那晚才刚开始
because that night was just beginning.